SwearNet.com Incorporated Privacy Policy
========================================

Version 1.2 : November 4, 2022
------------------------------

### 1\. Introduction

SwearNet.com is committed to safeguarding the privacy and security of your personal information. You should be familiar with how your personal information is collected, used and disclosed, as explained in this document.

1. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in conjunction with your access to any of our digital products and services.
    
2. Products covered by this Privacy Policy encompass all offerings owned and operated by SwearNet.com Incorporated, including the SwearNet.com, TrailerParkBoys.com and .org websites, email newsletters, social media pages, mobile apps and other applications owned and operated by us, our offline contacts, and to any other services that display this notice (collectively referred to as the “Swearnet.com Services”).
    
3. Where applicable, will apply the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the ePrivacy Directive (ePR) of the European Economic Union to all users, regardless of country of residence or region of access.
    
4. This policy applies to your personal data on SwearNet.com Services and pertains to the purpose and means of storing, processing and managing your personal data.
    
5. We use cookies to control access to our website. We will ask for your consent to use of cookies when you first visit our website.
    
6. Our website incorporates privacy controls which affect how we will process your personal data. By using the privacy controls, you can specify whether you would like to receive direct marketing communications and/or limit the publication of your information. You can access the privacy controls via your user profile.
    
7. In this policy, “you”, “your” and “yours” refer to you, the user of SwearNet.com Services.
    
8. In this policy, “we”, “us” and “our” refer to SwearNet.com Inc., the operator of SwearNet.com. See Section 14 for more information about our company, including contact information.

### 2\. How your personal data is collected

We and our service providers collect personal information in a variety of ways, including:

1. **Registration:** When you register for a SwearNet.com Service, we collect personal information. For example, registration on SwearNet.com can be done by supplying a unique email address and password, or by linking your Facebook account. See below under “Social-media platforms such as Facebook” for more information about linking your Facebook Account.
    
2. **Billing:** To subscribe to a SwearNet.com Service or enable payment, we collect and use your name and email address. Our payment providers collect additional information such as you credit or debit card information, and may also collect other personally identifiable information for the purpose of processing your payment.
    
3. **User-Generated Content and Public Activities (Including Comments):** We offer you opportunities to engage in public activities on SwearNet.com and other SwearNet.com Services. “Public activities” are any actions you take on SwearNet.com Services that are designed to be visible to other users, including comments, recommendations, reviews, ratings or any other items that you submit. If you choose to engage in public activities, you should be aware that any personal information you submit can be read, collected and used by other users of these services. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in the course of your public activities and we have no responsibility to publish, take down, remove or edit any of your public activities or submissions (except as required by applicable laws). For more information, please refer to the Terms of Service.
    
4. **Social-media platforms such as Facebook:** If you choose to link your social-media account or account relating to other third-party services to SwearNet.com Services, you may be asking third parties to send us certain information from those social media accounts or services accounts, and you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use what they send us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You can disassociate your SwearNet.com registration from third-party accounts any time.

### 3\. How your personal data is used

Your personal information is used to deliver our products and services to you, and sometimes, to improve the quality of our products services, as outlined below:

1. We collect, use or otherwise process personal information as allowed under applicable law, including where based on one or more of the following:
    
    * The consent you provide to us at the point of collection of your personal information;
        
    * The performance of the contract we have with you;
        
    * The compliance of a legal obligation to which we are subject; or
        
    * The legitimate interests of SwearNet.com Incorported, a third party or yourself.

    “Legitimate interest” is a technical term under the regulation. It means that there has to be good reason for the processing of your personal information, and that measures must be taken to minimize the impact on your privacy rights and interests. “Legitimate interest” also references our use of your data in ways you would reasonably expect, while having minimal privacy impact. We have a legitimate interest in collecting and processing personal information, for example: (a) to ensure that our networks and information are secure; (b) to administer and generally conduct business within SwearNet.com Incorporated and related services; and (c) to prevent fraud.
    
2. **Provide the SwearNet.com Services You Request:** We use the information we gather about you to enable your use of the SwearNet.com Services and fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as providing the SwearNet.com Services’ functionality to you, arranging access to your registered account, providing you with customer service, responding to your inquiries, requests, questions, suggestions, compliments or complaints, completing your transactions, sending you administrative information (such as change of our terms, conditions, or policies), maintaining your list of favourite videos, and enabling you to participate in and renew paid services, polls, promotions, surveys, panels or research, and message boards. We will engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you or comply with a legal obligation.
    
3. **Analysis and Development of New Products and Services:** We perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users of the SwearNet.com Services, and their subscribing and purchasing patterns, so we can analyze or predict our users’ preferences for product and services development purposes, to determine our promotional campaign effectiveness so we can adapt our campaign to the needs and interests of our users, and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base. We use this information for analytical purposes, including analysis to improve customer relationships, to support strategic business decisions and our marketing tactics and to measure and track our brand health. We will engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you, to comply with a legal obligation, or because we have a legitimate interest in doing so.
    
4. **Customizing Your Experience:** We use the information that we have to better understand you and customize certain features of the SwearNet.com Services to provide you with an enhanced experience including to show you offerings, promotions or products that may be of interest to you, based on the demographic information, type of device you are using to access the SwearNet.com Services, your usage of the SwearNet.com Services and your reading history. We will provide personalized services because we have a legitimate interest.
    
5. **Email Newsletters, Marketing Activities and Social Sharing:** When you sign up for email newsletters, SwearNet.com will periodically send you email newsletters or promotional emails about content and services offered by SwearNet.com Services. To opt out of these emails, please see the section labeled How do I opt out from receiving emails? We will use the information we have about you to advertise our services to you on our SwearNet.com Services but also on other platforms. If you choose to use social-sharing functionalities, we will use your information to facilitate such action, and such action – along with any information you share – will be covered by the social-media platform’s privacy policy. We will engage in these activities with your consent or where we have a legitimate interest.
    
6. **Administrative Purposes:** We and our service providers use the information we have about you for the following legitimate business purposes:
    
    * For auditing purposes, to verify that our internal processes function as intended and comply with legal, regulatory and contractual requirements;
        
    * For fraud and security monitoring purposes, including, for example, to detect and prevent cyberattacks; and
        
    * To understand and assess satisfaction with our SwearNet.com Services or our customer care team.

    We engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you, to comply with a legal obligation, or because we have a legitimate interest.
    
7. **Allowing You to Participate in Contests or Other Promotions:** We may offer you the opportunity to participate in contests or other promotions. Some of these promotions have additional rules containing information about how we will use and disclose your personal information. We use this information to manage our contractual relationship with you.
    
8. **Aggregating and/or Anonymising Personal Information:** We aggregate and/or anonymize personal information so that it will no longer be considered personally identifying. We do so to generate other data for our use, which we may use and disclose for any purpose.
    
9. **User Generated Content and Public Activities:** When you share or recommend links to content on a social-media platform (such as Facebook, Google+ and Twitter), that action and any information you share will be covered by that platform’s privacy policy. Any information you disclose in your public activities, along with your screen name or ID, or any image or photo, becomes public.

### 4\. How your personal data is processed

1. This section covers:
    
    * the general categories of personal data that we may process;
        
    * in the case of personal data that we did not obtain directly from you, the source and specific categories of that data;
        
    * the purposes for which we may process personal data; and
        
    * the legal bases of the processing.
        
2. We may process data concerning access to SwearNet.com Services, otherwise known as **usage data**. Usage data may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, device type, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is Google Analytics and service access logs. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of understanding the general usage patterns of our customer base, improving our services or investigating service quality, or security incidents. The legal basis for usage data processing is our legitimate interests in maintaining the highest levels of service quality, availability and content to our members.
    
3. We may process data relating to your account, referred to as **account data**. Your account data consists of your email address and a password that you have selected. The source of your account data is you when you registered with the site. Your account data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining backups of our membership data and for communication with you. The legal basis for this processing is your consent when you registered with the site and our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.
    
4. We may process your information included in your personal profile on our services, referred to as **profile data**. The profile data may include your name, address, email address, social media account names (such as Skype, Twitter, and Facebook), profile pictures, gender, date of birth. The profile data may be processed for the purposes of enabling and monitoring your use of our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is your consent and our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our services and business.
    
5. We may process your personal data that are provided in the course of the use of our services, referred to as **service data**. The service data may include access details to external vendors that we rely on to provide content and services, merchandise or other similar services to you. The source of the service data is your access to our site. The service data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of SwearNet.com Services and our business.
    
6. We may process information that you post for publication on our website or through our services, known as **publication data**. The publication data may be processed for the purposes of enabling such publication and administering our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is your consent and our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our services and business.
    
7. We may process information contained in any enquiry you submit to us regarding goods and/or services, known as **enquiry data**. The enquiry data may be processed for the purposes of resolving a service or technical issue, offering, marketing and selling relevant goods and/or services to you. The legal basis for this processing is your consent and our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our services and business.
    
8. We may process information relating to our customer relationships, including customer contact information, known as **customer relationship data**. The customer relationship data may include your name, your contact details, and information exchanged in communications with you. The source of the customer relationship data is you. The customer relationship data may be processed for the purposes of managing our relationships with customers, communicating with customers, keeping records of those communications and promoting our products and services to customers. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper management of our customer relationships.
    
9. We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of goods and services, that you enter into with us and/or through our services, referred to as **transaction data**. The transaction data may include your contact details, your card details and the details of the purchase transaction. The transaction data may be processed for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and keeping proper records of those transactions. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract and our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our services and business.
    
10. We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters, known as **notification data**. The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us, at your request, to enter into such a contract.
    
11. We may process information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us, referred to as **correspondence data**. The correspondence data may include the communication content and metadata associated with the communication. Our website will generate the metadata associated with communications made using the website’s contact forms. The correspondence data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and for our record keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our services and business and communications with users.
    
12. We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others.
    
13. We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, or obtaining professional advice. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper protection of our business against risks.
    
14. In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal data set out in this section, we may also process any of your personal data where such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.
    
15. Please do not supply any other person’s personal data to us, unless we specifically prompt you to do so.

### 5\. Providing your personal data to others

1. We may disclose your personal data to any member of our group of companies (meaning our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes, and on the legal bases, set out in this policy.
    
2. We may disclose your personal data to our insurers and/or professional advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, obtaining professional advice, or the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.
    
3. Financial transactions relating to our services and services are handled by our payment services providers PayPal and Stripe. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. You can find information about the payment services providers’ privacy policies and practices at PayPal.com and Stripe.com.
    
4. We may disclose your enquiry data to one or more of those selected third party suppliers of goods and services identified on our website for the purpose of enabling them to contact you so that they can offer, market and sell to you relevant goods and/or services. Each such third party will act as a data controller in relation to the enquiry data that we supply to it; and upon contacting you, each such third party will supply to you a copy of its own privacy policy, which will govern that third party’s use of your personal data.
    
5. In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this section, we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.

### 6\. International transfers of your personal data

1. In this section, we provide information about the circumstances in which your personal data may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA).
    
2. We, and our group of companies, have offices in Canada. The European Commission has made an “adequacy decision” with respect to the data protection laws in Canada. Transfers to Canada will be protected appropriate safeguards, namely the use of standard data protection clauses adopted or approved by the European Commission, a copy of which can be obtained from https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield\_en
    
3. The hosting facilities for our services are situated in Canada and the United States of America. The European Commission has made an “adequacy decision” with respect to the data protection laws of each of these countries. Transfers to each of these countries will be protected by appropriate safeguards, namely the use of standard data protection clauses adopted or approved by the European Commission, a copy of which you can obtain from https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield\_en
    
4. Payment transactions are situated in the United States of America, namely PayPal and Stripe. The European Commission has made an “adequacy decision” with respect to the data protection laws in the United States of America. Transfers to the United States of America will be protected by appropriate safeguards, namely the use of standard data protection clauses adopted or approved by the European Commission, a copy of which can be obtained from https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield\_en
    
5. You acknowledge that personal data that you submit for publication through our website or services may be available, via the Internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use (or misuse) of such personal data by others.

### 7\. Retaining and deleting personal data

1. This section sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal data.
    
2. Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
    
3. We will retain your personal data as follows:
    
    1. **Usage Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years following their creation, to a maximum period of 5 years following their collection date.
        
    2. **Account Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years, to a maximum period of 5 years following their last date of access, or until deletion is requested by you, the registered user.
        
    3. **Profile Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years following their creation, to a maximum period of 5 years following their creation date.
        
    4. **Service Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years following their creation, to a maximum period of 5 years following their creation date.
        
    5. **Publication Data** will be retained for an indefinite period of time, until deleted by you, or until deletion is requested by you, the registered user.
        
    6. **Enquiry Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years following their request date, to a maximum period of 5 years following their last access, entry or update.
        
    7. **Customer Relationship Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years following their creation date, to a maximum period of 5 years following their last access, entry or update.
        
    8. **Transaction Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years following their creation, to a maximum period of 5 years following their last update.
        
    9. **Notification Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years, to a maximum period of 5 years following their creation.
        
    10. **Correspondance Data** will be retained for a minimum period of 2 years following their creation, to a maximum period of 5 years following their last update.
        
4. In some cases it is not possible for us to specify in advance the periods for which your personal data will be retained. In such cases, we will determine the period of retention based on the following criteria:
    
    (a) the period of retention of any personal information not categorized above will be determined based on business requirements, typically to our minimum required business or legal obligation.
    
    (b) in some cases, when a user has a legitimate privacy issue or extenuating circumstance, we may delete data earlier than the published period.
    
5. Notwithstanding the other provisions above, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

### 8\. Amendments

1. We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.
    
2. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy.
    
3. We will attempt to notify you of significant changes to this policy by email and/or messaging on our website.

### 9\. Your rights

1. In this section, we have summarized the rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights.
    
2. Your principal rights under data protection law are:
    
    1. the right to access;
        
    2. the right to rectification;
        
    3. the right to erasure;
        
    4. the right to restrict processing;
        
    5. the right to object to processing;
        
    6. the right to data portability;
        
    7. the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and
        
    8. the right to withdraw consent.
        
3. You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee. You can access your personal data by visiting your user profile when logged into our website.
    
4. You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.
    
5. In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: the personal data is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal data have been unlawfully processed. However, there are exclusions of the right to erasure. The general exclusions include where processing is necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.
    
6. In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.
    
7. You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
    
8. You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose.
    
9. You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes on grounds relating to your particular situation, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.
    
10. To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal data is:
    1. your consent; or
    2. that the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract, and such processing is carried out by automated means, You have the right to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.
11. If you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.
    
12. To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.
    
13. You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by serving written notice to us or by any method specified in Section 14.

### 10\. About cookies

1. A cookie is a file stored locally in your browser that contains an identifier (a string of letters and numbers). These identifiers are sent back to the server with each browser request in order to maximize security, enhance performance and persist preferences.
    
2. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.
    
3. Cookies on their own do not typically contain personal information or data, our cookies do not store personal data, but cookie identifiers do link to your data stored on our servers and databases.
    
4. For maximum security, all swearnet.com cookies are signed and set with the following attributes: Secure, HttpOnly, and where possible SameSite = Strict.
    
5. Please refer to the section on [Cookie Management](#cookie_management) for information on managing your browser’s cookie permissions and privacy options.
    
6. For an in depth technical explanation of cookies, please refer to this external link: [How Google Uses Cookies](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies).

### 11\. Cookies set by Swearnet

Swearnet.com uses the following cookies:

1. **Session State**
    
    * Name: \_swearnet\_session
    * Type: Session
    * Use: This session cookie is used for personalization, what are are permitted to see and do on our website as well as access to data you have explicitly chosen to store on our webserver. This cookie assigns a unique identifier that allows Swearnet to identify you whenever you connect to our server. After sign in, this cookie is used to recover your user profile, determine your purchases, validate your membership and other personal aspects related to your use of the website.
    * Creation: It is created upon your initial visit to our website.
    * Expiry: Modern browsers will delete this cookie and other session cookies after you close your browsing session.
2. **Remember Me**
    
    * Name: remember\_user\_token
    * Type: Persistent
    * Use: It allows Swearnet to authenticate you without the need for you to provide your email and password each time you connect to our website, even after you have closed or ended your browsing session. For this reason, it is not recommended to activate “Remember me” on a public computer.
    * Creation: This cookie will be activated when the “Remember me for 2 months” checkbox is checked during sign in.
    * Expiry: This cookie will have an expiry date of two months from the date of activation. In other words, after two years, users will have to provide username and password once again. This cookie will be deleted when you explicitly “Logout” of the website.
3. **Consent to Cookie Use**
    
    * Name: \_\_consented\_to\_cookies
    * Type: Persistent
    * Use: This cookie identifies that you have accepted use of our cookies when visiting our site.
    * Creation: It is created upon your acceptance of cookie use the first time you visit our site.
    * Expiry: It will expire after two years, at which time we will ask for your permission to use cookies again.
4. **Terms and Conditions Acceptance**
    
    * Name: \_\_consented\_to\_terms
    * Type: Persistent
    * Use: This cookie identifies that you have accepted our Terms and Conditions for using our site.
    * Creation: It is created upon your acceptance of our Terms when you sign up for our site.
    * Expiry: It will expire after two years, at which time we will ask for your acceptance again.

### 12\. Cookies used by our service providers

Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website. These include:

1. Vidyard.com : We rely on Vidyard to deliver the majority of streamed video content. There are a handful of cookies that Vidyard uses to improve and track video playback. The cookies are used to deliver optimized content, performance tracking and user analytics. See vidyard.com for more information about these cookies.
    
2. Stripe.com : We use Stripe for payment processing, generally improving privacy and security of credit/debit card payments.
    
3. Disqus.com : We use Disqus as a service for user generated comments. Disqus stores a number of cookies for authentication, authorization and tracking.
    
4. YouTube.com : Some video, particularly user generated video, may be delivered via YouTube. Google stores cookies to improve and track video playback. The cookies are used to deliver optimized content, performance tracking and user analytics.
    
5. Google.com : We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. A Google Analytic cookie is created when you first visit our website and is updated as you navigate our website. For additional information, please refer to Google’s Analytic Cookie Usage and Privacy Policy.

### 13\. Cookie Management

1. Most browsers allow you to block cookies, as well as options to delete cookies. These methods vary among browser brands and releases. You can either follow instructions below or access help documentation for up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies.
    
2. Blocking cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability most websites, including SwearNet.com.
    
3. If you all block cookies, you will not be able to access all of the features on our website.
    
4. **Google Chrome Cookie Management**
    
    To block ALL third-party cookies in Google Chrome:
    
    * Click the three vertical dots in the upper-right corner
    * Select Settings
    * Select Privacy and security
    * Select Cookies and other site data
    * Select Block third-party cookies
    
    If you want specific sites to collect both first-party and third-party cookies, or if you don’t want specific websites to store anything:
    
    * As in the previous instructions, go to Settings → Privacy and Security → Cookies and other site data
    * Scroll down to the Customized behaviours section
    * Select Add next to Sites that can always use cookies or Sites that can never use cookies
    * Enter the site URL in the Site textbox fields
    * If you want the rule to apply to all cookies, check the Including third-party cookies on this site checkbox
    * Select Add
5. **Safari Cookie Management**
    
    Safari blocks third-party cookies by default. To confirm this in your Safari for macOS:
    
    * Click on the Safari menu and select Preferences
    * Select the Privacy tab
    * Confirm that Prevent cross-site tracking is checked
    
    For precise cookie settings, under the Privacy tab, select Manage Website Data. This will list all websites currently storing cookies in Safari. From this list you can select a website and delete stored cookies by clicking Remove. Just a caution that Remove All will remove all cookies from Safari, which is something you likely don’t want to do!
    
6. **Mozilla Firefox Cookie Management**
    
    Mozilla Firefox offers three levels of privacy protection: Standard, Strict and Custom, which are as follows:
    
    * Standard privacy: third-party cookies are blocked only in private windows
    * Strict privacy: very secure to the point that there is the risk that some sites will not work properly
    * Custom privacy: allows you to choose which cookies to block, which is what we will be setting now
    
    To set the custom privacy options (recommended):
    
    * Click on the three horizontal bars in the upper-right corner
    * Select Settings
    * Select Privacy & Security (the lock icon)
    * Select Custom
    * Click the drop-down menu to the right of the Cookies option, and select All third-party cookies
    
    To block or allow all cookies on specific websites:
    
    * Select Settings → Privacy & Security
    * Scroll down to Cookies and Site Data
    * Select the Manage Exceptions… button
    * In the window that opens, enter the URL of the site you want to block or allow to use cookies
    * Select Block or Allow
    * Click Save Changes
7. **Microsoft Edge Cookie Management**
    
    To block third-party cookies in Microsoft Edge:
    
    * Select the three dots icon in the upper-right corner
    * Select Settings.
    * In the left-hand menu, select Cookies and site permissions
    * Go to Manage and delete cookies and site data
    * Enable Block third-party cookies
    
    To create an exclusions list:
    
    * Go to Settings → Cookies and site permissions → Manage and delete cookies and site data
    * Select Add next to Block and/or Allow
    * Enter the URLs in the relevant fields and check the Include third-party cookies on this site box

### 14\. Our details

1. This website is owned and operated by SwearNet.com Incorporated.
    
2. We are registered as an incorporated business in Dartmouth, Nova Scotia Canada.
    
3. Our principal business postal address is:
    
         SwearNet.com Incorporated
         P.O. Box 38072 Burnside
         Dartmouth NS
         B3B 1X2
         CANADA

4. You can contact us:
    
    1. by post, using the postal address above;
        
    2. using our website contact form;
        
    3. by email, using [\[email protected\]](https://www.swearnet.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### 15\. Data protection officer

1. Requests and questions concerning data privacy are best directed to our data protection officer via email: John Andrews [\[email protected\]](https://www.swearnet.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
    
2. For written requests, our data protection officer can be reached at:
    
         John Andrews
         CTO, SwearNet.com Incorporated
         PO Box 38072 Burnside
         Dartmouth NS
         B3B 1X2
         CANADA

© 2013 - 2024 SwearNet.com Incorporated. All rights reserved. [HOME](https://www.swearnet.com/) | [PRIVACY](https://www.swearnet.com/privacy) | [TERMS](https://www.swearnet.com/terms) | [HELP](https://www.swearnet.com/faq)
